Hello and welcome back.
So in the previous section we had a look how we can build the SDK.
So here we are going to do a practical session.
So let's go ahead to the terminal.
Okay?
So let's see the commands we need to build the setup to research this.
Already done.
I'll just go start with this part.
So it's just lunch.
Just run it.
So you have a new way right now in G and the platform is then the target product is SDK.
So everything has got changed.
So in case if you have limited hard disk, but just make sure that you have enough disk space before
doing this.
Okay, so let's go ahead and start make just check EVE 16 JS 16 SDK.
It started.
So it's just started now.
So it'll take a while.
So I'll just go ahead and post my video and then I'll come back.
Okay.
So finally the build process is completed.
So it took one hour, 20 minutes and 23 minutes and 49 seconds.
Okay.
So let's go ahead and have a look at the output.
So the right path is actually under our host and this is the build which you have done and then the
SDK SDK folder.
And here you have these two folders and so so you can copy this and share with your developers.
So this is the one this is the correct one, which is having a 23.6 MP.
So you can either host it locally in your local web server or maybe you can upload it in somewhere over
the Internet so that you are developers can use that in Android studio.
So I'll just quickly show you how you can access this in Android studio.
So if you come to Android studio, you have got something like the Tools SDK manager, you have something
like SDK update sites here.
You can actually refer for those stickers.
So here you can just add basically have to add it over here and then just go ahead and download and
use it.
Okay.
So that's it for this session.